Please marry me
Can you promise?
That you'll always be truthful?
If you're her aunt, how can you not say anything when your niece is staying over with a man?
That's not right!
Go, quickly and show me the way.
If you know she's staying over with a guy, just tell her to quickly come home.
Why do you feel the need to go over there?
Hah, just know that you became a doctor's wife thanks to me.
Mom's coming over.
What?!
My mom don't like it.
Why?
We've already dated for 5 years
I've slept with you countless times.
and I'm more concerned about this lamp more than sleeping with you right now.
Sleeping with you is not the same thing as loving you.
It's just all physical.
- Then let's get married
- What? What?
My mother-in-law is wacky.
I would have just let it go
if you were a stranger...
But I couldn't just let it go since you're Ki Joon's little brother.
I guess your Mother's blood does run in your veins.
No, I just gave you the okay before I even asked her about it.
You keep taking her side and it's starting to get annoying.
-Hae Yoon
-Why are you here?
Are you crazy?!
Wow... Today really stinks.
Being cast suspicious over a man I don't feel anything for after getting dumped.
Do you know how it feels to be broken up with?
Dong Bi!
Is this where Ha Dong Gun lives?
Yes he lives in that house
They are amazing people.
And the Madame is an angel.
[ Episode 2: 130 days before the wedding, meet the parents ]
Is there something you're looking for?
What do you have that's good for an older woman?
This is soaked in honey. even those who can't eat red ginseng can eat this without worry.
Is it okay for my fiancé's parent's?
If you want that
Buy this
I think this would be good for that
How much is it?
[ A total of 320, 00 was charged to your card. ]
Yes Hyung
I told Min Ho to come over later.
Since he's been married twice,
he would know how to behave at the in-laws very well.
You're right.
He's about to become useful.
Where are you right now? Are you outside?
Oh I was just at the mall buying a gift.
But..
I'm spending way too much money.
I'm scared of my credit card bill for this month.
We don't need this, Mom.
-You don't need it for japchae? - I'm making mushroom Japchae.
Then you can just use it later.
Spinach doesn't keep well. You need to buy it when you need it.
The one who married you sure is lucky.
You're good at homemaker, and gave him a son...
and you don't even use anyone to help you
maintain that big house and you're young.
You're not lacking in anything.
I don't think he thinks that way.
Women who live as well as you usually don't get treated as well.
Men think that what you are doing is a given.
You have to tell them off once in awhile for them to have some respect.
-But since you're so good at everything...
-I'm doing it all for my own sake.
What do you mean, it's for your sake?
I'm training him so that he can't do a thing if I'm not around.
So that even if he does have an affair,
he won't be able to leave me.
-Is he having an affair?
-No, I keep a very close eye on him.
I know everything that he's up to.
But start putting aside a nest egg.
One must prepare themselves for a good rainy day when things are going good.
Mom, you really are something.
Why don't you tell Hae Yoon to keep the option of divorce in mind when she gets married?
- I think I should marry Hae Yoon off.
- Why the sudden change of mind.
That family has a lot of money.
I've checked it all out.
And I told Hae Yoon to find out his parent's social security number.
- You really are...
- Let's go get some meat. Hanwoo
No need for huge concern. She's just dehydrated.
She can be discharged once the IV is done.
Call me and let me know if there's a change.
Yes, Thank you.
Do you like him that much?
He hasn't called me once...
or even texted.
- I think it's really over.
- How could he be like this?
Even a dog shouldn't be treated like this.
You've been dating for five years, how could he do this to you?
You were always so good to him!
You even put an ad for his restaurant in a magazine to advertise it..
and you waited on him hand and foot when he was sick.
Aunt..
In any case, I think there's something wrong with me.
Even after all this, I still don't hate him..
and I want him to tell me he wants me back.
I'm not going to let that bastard get away with this.
But what if I listen to you guys and things go downhill?
Come on... I've been married twice.
I'm successful at getting married... just not maintaining it.
What are you curious about?
Is getting a red ginseng sent appropriate for her mother? There is only her mother.
That's a bit so-so.
The first one is the France anti-aging cream
She totally fell for it.
And for my second mother-in-law . . .
Your explanation is always so long.
Forget it, I'll just take it to her.
You are so critical.
You never let me finish what I'm saying.
What would you like to order?
I haven't seen you around. How old are you?
What? I've been here for a month now.
So what I'm saying is, how old are you? -I'm 25.
Ah.. it's over for you after this year.
Girls that are 25 are my favourite.
Oppa, what would you like to order? - I have another dinner appointment.
I don't have dinner plans.
What should I have?
That's what Ajusshi should tell me.
Why does she look so grumpy?
You should fire her.
She's so rude.
She brings a lot of customers.
Hyung, you're the one who shouldn't come.
Don't fire her then.
Keep your spirits up.
Thanks Unni!
Why didn't you arrive together with Sung Joon?
We were going to meet at the restaurant, but I didn't want to see Ki Joon Oppa.
So I just told him to call me when he gets here.
Why are you being like that to Ki Joon because of Dong Bi?
My friend's enemy is my enemy.
Mm, it's tasty.
But why hasn't our aunt come yet?
I hate you.
I don't know how to handle it when someone who's old enough to be my Dad acts up.
Wow, she's got some attitude. She's cute.
What is her deal?
She's kind of cute.
Even though I haven't learned anything, I need to get going.
Tell her all the food is delicious
And you better eat two servings of rice. - I know that too, hyung.
You better get going, you're going to be late.
Got it.
Aunt!
Noonim (respectful term for older sis), do you recognize me?
Why don't you take a seat here?
I was just about to go. Did you come knowing I was here?
You know Ki Joong right?
I know. I know about him well, Dong Bi has told me about him.
Dong Bi and I have broken up.
You broke up? When?
Maybe a week ago?
- You must be sad.
- Why sad?
It's been five years, we grew tired of each other.
- Aunt! - You got sick of her?
You dated for five years and you got sick of her?
Dong Bi, from breaking up with a guy like you
she hasn''t even been able to drink water,
and had to be taken to the emergency room.
But don't you think you're still overreacting?
Yes, I'm overreacting.
Even though I'm not blood related, I'm overreacting again.
Dong Bi is someone who is precious to me.
There's been many times I've helped her pick out gifts for you.
and when she sued to worry about you,
I used to try to cheer her up.
I should be allowed to have a say in your relationship.
Aun't let's go outside.
No matter how angry you are,
this is still a place of business.
But she still says that she loves you.
and doesn't hate you, only wanting you to contact her.
This is what you call love.
Something someone like you will never understand in his lifetime.
Let go of me.
I have to go to Dong Bi's place. I should make some congee for her to eat tomorrow.
Go quickly to the house.
-I'll take you to Dong Bi's.
- No, it's okay. Go now so you won't be late.
-But still...
- Don't tell Hae Yoon... What I did.
I just realized myself that I can be violent like this.
Are you afraid?
I'm afraid Hae Yoon would be embrassed of me.
Wait here just a moment, okay?
Hyung, I think you'll have to escort Aunt to Dong Bi's place.
I don't want to. What if she throws water in my face too?
If she does..
It'll be good for you anyways.
Hey, hey...how is that good?
Okay, I got it.
Aunt, Hyung Min Ho will escort you.
That's okay. I can go by myself.
- It doesn't take long in a taxi.
-I have a bike too.
That would make me feel better.
I don't want to!
I don't even know this man!
Sis.. Do you see me as a man?
Don't do that..
I've never dated an older woman before,
So I'm pretty inexperienced with that.
Why don't you hang out with any normal men?
Hyung is just joking, he usually is like this.
- I wasn't joking, Sis.
- Why do you keep calling me that?
How do you think it seems when an old guy calls you an older sister?
Since you're old enough,
be more considerate of other's feelings.
I can't ride my bike with someone who disrespect me like this either.
- Hold on tight if you're scared.
- Can you go a little faster?
Let's go!
What is this?
I'm going to give this to your mother.
This is my company's new product. It means I will become her pet like this.
I'm sorry for ruining the mood, but my mom doesn't like these sorts of things.
Then what do I do?
This was part of my plan.
Should I put it back in the car?
No, even if she doesn't like it, you need to show her what you prepared.
It shows her that you're making an effort.
How do my clothes look?
- Let's see.
- How is it? Do you like it?
Honey, even if my mom acts in an offensive way, you must not be mad at me.
It's so cute!
You didn't need to bring me this from work!
Thank you for liking it.
I would like to formally introduce myself.
It's good you came.
Look at him.
- You look handsome.
- You too, hyung.
He isn't your hyung, he is going to become your uncle.
Yes, he is going to marry your aunt.
Thank you, mother.
Mom.
I welcome those who my daughter has chosen.
I will take care of her all my life.
Of course you must.
- Talk in a casual way, mother.
- I will the next time I see you.
I prepared food, but I don't know if it will fit to your liking.
I will eat anything that you make.
We need to prepare the table.
I'll do it. Where is the table?
Grandma, can't you give that toy to me?
No I can't because it was given to me as a present by somebody special.
You aren't supposed to give away gifts.
I have something for Tae Won here!
Wow!
- As expected...
- What?
Normally when young women take off their helmet and reveal their face, you fall in love with them.
As expected, when the woman is too old, when she takes her helmet and reveals her face, there is nothing.
I just figured it out today.
Since I don't let an old woman ride on the bike.
What a weirdo.
- What's your name?
- What is it yo you?
You told me not too call you noonim.
Since we have no reason to meet again, there is no reason to call me again.
So you don't need to know my name.
Why don't we see each other again?
We'll see each other at the wedding!
Seriously.. what are you upset about?
Do you by any chance have feelings for me, noonim?
It's Lee Deul Rae.
Lee Deul Rae.
Her first name is pretty, but when you put it together with her last name it's Lee Deul Rae.
Lee Deul Rae...want to cause some trouble?
( word play on her name)
Should I get you more soup?
Yes, it tastes really good.
She did everything.
She does very well in housekeeping. It's because she takes after me.
Before I get married, I need to learn from her.
You'll be fine once you get to it, so don't worry too much.
Also, in the beginning of a marriage, they always say it tastes good even if it doesn't.
Does everyone do that?
It's because your husband takes care of you.
They say that as long as they love their wife, they'll accept just about anything.
Do Hyun bought this for me,
and even though I don't like frivolous things.
Even if I tell him he shouldn't, he keeps buying it for me.
You should have told your husband to come as well.
We saw him occasionally, but
it wasn't when the entire family was together.
I think he had a night surgery.
He couldn't refuse because they are V.I.P.
Oppa.
Don't leave too much for us and take it with you.
Hye Yoon and Deul Rae don't eat much at home.
You can eat it.
Is your husband home? Why don't you try calling him?
I did a moment before. If I call him again, he will get pissed.
Why should he get pissed? It's a good thing for wife to be concerned.
I heard only dogs go out to greet a man once he's over the age of 40.
Hye Yoon is very pretty. I envy her.
Since the man is young, he has soft fine hair too.
He does look cute.
He seems like a young gentleman who hasn't gone through much hardships.
I didn't even get to date like that,
and got married after scurrying around being scared all the time.
But the man is rich. That's enough.
For him, his parents have all the money. It's hard to take the parent's wealth.
- I think I need to go now.
- Don't go.
What would I do if I don't go?
Let's sleep.
You are crazy. Don't you know mom is waiting inside?
I know.
But I still don't want to be apart from you.
Me too.
Let's get married quickly.
Did unni leave?
- Thank you.
- About what?
For warmly welcoming him.
- You knew too, right?
- About what?
You are so fox like.
What?
Their family is rich.
It seems doctors gain a lot of money
Land, house, building. They have an apartment in the center of Gangnam.
They have a very good reputation as well. You hit the jackpot.
Is that why?
Then why would I?
Because he is handsome?
Being handsome is only good once when you walk down the aisle with him.
You are a very scary person.
Thank you, aunt.
I don't know how much you are hurting because I haven't loved.
How I acted when my mom died and how you are acting right now
is the same so I'm thinking it's something similar.
I just don't want to do anything.
How could I become like this because of a man?
- Don't go.
- I need to go.
Just for a day, I wish we can be in the same place comfortably.
That depends on how you make up your mind. I'm going.
Who are you?
Then who are you?
I'm the owner of this seat.
I'm the person covering for the owner of this desk.
Dong Bi, it's been a long time.
Why did you come out?
I'm sorry for not calling you and being absent without notice.
- And bailing out on you...
- Yeah, I like that.
You know well what you did wrong.
- I will make sure things like this doesn't happen again.
- Of course.
No, nothing like that would happen again.
Since I found somebody to replace you.
- Pardon?
- I liked you for working well.
and this is how you repay the favor?
Aunt!
You look better. Is there good news?
- It's alright.
- Is my pizza ready?
Just wait a little bit.
Sit down.
What?
To be honest, I was curious about something so I made the excuse of wanting pizza to come.
You are curious about me?
What could you be curious about?
- Do you like me?
- Don't talk rubbish!
- It's about Hye Yoon's sister. Is it true?
- About what?
I heard it from my sister. You would have told her.
You might think it isn't important because it isn't about you.
But I don't believe that a person can be that nonchalant.
I believe that a person's family dynamics can affect the type of person you are.
I don't know what you heard from my mom, aunt.
But I observed Jung Hoon and Hye Yoon dating for a few years.
When Jung Hoon is with Hye Yoon, he smiles a lot.
It is not common to come across of woman who can make somebody smile.
It wasn't even said through the person directly involved.
If they found out that you are background checking through rumours
they will just offend them.
Oh my goodness! How is this background checking?
- Here is your pizza.
- Thank you.
What did you tell aunt for her to come chasing after me?
I told you just so you only know.
Why do you have a big mouth?
So why do you have to hear from me that you have a big mouth?
From now on, don't be involved in Jung Hoon's marriage.
Don't make it difficult.
Did you wait a long time?
I got fired.
She gave away my position to another person.
How are you handling all this?
It's a little sad, but it's not to the point that I want to die.
- You don't want to die?
- I don't want to die because of work.
Is work a big deal? I can just find another one.
Love is a bigger problem because it can't be found.
Come down.
When the department store closes, I have to make my own clothes and wear them.
It looks too much like a teacher.
- You think so too?
- Change up your style.
You're too rigid.
Those are the words I hate the most.
Rigid and pragmatic.
- What about this?
- I'll have to try it on.
This is so expensive.
- Be quiet. Somebody will hear.
- Why does it matter if they hear?
It's the truth that it's expensive.
- Do you have to be so cheap?
-Are you going to charge it?
I have a card with no interest for three months.
I was wondering if you were going to make it
since you couldn't even drink a sip of water.
You are alive now.
So are you depressed?
You guys are fighting over eating again.
We aren't fighting.
As a friend, I was just testing her fighting power for eating to see if she was back to normal.
Alright, you should eat a lot.
Dong Bi.
There's no man that's good enough in this world for you to stop breathing.
I know men well. So don't risk your life over a man.
Then what about me?
You have already risked your life.
Don't think about anything else.
Eat.
Crazy people.
Yes, it's the daycare center.
Yes, I understand.
You must come before 6:30.
Yes.
I keep seeing the bike in front of me.
How much would the bike that the man with a square head
and a stomach that protrudes and wears a colorful bandana rides cost?
Take out a lot this time. It is really hard to manage.
It's because you follow women in their twenties at your age.
Then don't you meet women in their twenties?
I am younger than you are.
You are fifty the day after tomorrow.
Age is nothing but a number. Isn't it a famous saying?
Why is age nothing but a number? Do you know how honest your body is?
You aren't cool!
Don't get skimpy because you're doing this for free.
Do it with care.
You might just get yourself a new sister-in-law this year.
You are going to marry again?
I want to have children, Do Hyun.
Even if I have a child right now, they will be still in elementary school when I become sixty.
Don't laugh.
Wait a just a moment.
Director, you have a guest.
I visited because I missed you.
Are you mad?
A person can be like that from time to time. What can I do when I want to see you like crazy?
I can't?
You can from time to time.
You can't too occasionally.
Hey!
Lee Dong Bi
Lee Dong Bi!
Hey!
Are you hurt?
I'm alright.
You said you would never come back.
What's up?
Does your heart beat? Do you even have a heart?
How can you be so unaffected?
We dated for five years!
Even if a dog in the neighborhood suddenly went missing, I would go searching for it out of curiosity.
Am I nothing compared to a dog?
Why are you making a fuss over trying to live like other people?
When we first started, we said we would ignore marriage systems
and relationships between a man and a woman and would find our own way.
But I like you, and because I like you I want to go to you, what can I do about that?
What can I do when I want to draw a border around you
so nobody can see you or have you.
Since I can't accept your demands
I didn't hold on to you when you left.
I understand.
I understood you fully.
I'll go.
Where are you going?
Do it properly! The angle isn't right!
Do it like this.
Okay, that's good.
That's pretty good.
I do everything well when I am taught.
-Do you want to drink?
- No.
Because I'll get buzzed if I have a drink,
and if I get buzzed, I may want to have sex.
You changed to much recently.
I can't get used to it.
How did expressing your feelings become so straightforward?
Once I started letting it all out, I think my heart is getting lighter.
To add on to that, since I got fired, I have nothing to lose.
You got fire? You didn't leave?
Yes, I got fired.
I thought that reporter thing was going to work out for you
what are you going to do?
I'm not going to fold these.
I put herb oil because I thought you had a lot of surgeries and was tired.
You feel feel less exhausted.
Car center.
Hello, this is Nam Do Hyun's cell phone.
Hey!
You are going to work without eating?
I'm late. I told Hye Yoon I would drive her to work.
Is Hye Yoon sick? Is that why you are driving her to work?
- I'm just doing it.
- Is she coming tomorrow?
- Like last time...
- I told you that last time was my fault.
- Why are you throwing a fit?
- I'll go now.
You like her that much?
What's wrong?
I think I am a mother in law.
I want to act like a mother in law because I think she is making him suffer.
Don't come. I'm just going to take the taxi.
I told you not to come. Even if you come right now, I'll be late.
I'm late because you told me you would come.
You just go off to work.
- I'm hungry.
- Me too.
In dramas, the woman would pack lunch and feed it to the man driving.
Dramas are just dramas. Let's not compare.
- Let's go to MT
- Where? What's MT?
M.O.T.E.L... MT.
I figured when you told me you would drive me to work.
You are not the person to make a move without a goal.
A person?
Goal?
Fine. Let's go to MT today.
You think I'm some sort of a beast?
that you won't go?
Why are you getting mad at somebody going to work in the morning?
Would I be able to work when you are being like this?
Are you the only one going to work. I am too.
Do you really need to talk like that in the morning?
What do you mean, someone? What a nice thing for a teacher to be teaching to her students.
Okay. Fine, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said that.
But you think you're being any better for asking like this over my slip of the tongue?
It's because I am mad.
Should you just say anything because you are mad?
You can't take back words that have been spoken.
Does it all end when you say it didn't mean anything when you have already hurt somebody's heart?
Yes, when somebody else does it, it's an affair and when you do it, it's romance.
- What?
- You were the first one to hurt me.
I am a person who wouldn't make a move without a goal?
How do you think about me normally?
You couldn't have said that without thinking about me like that normally.
Would I have decided to marry you if I normally think of you in that way?
Why do you think we keep fighting?
Why do you think we jump at such little things as if our life is on the line?
I think I have problems.
I'm sorry for ruining your morning.
If you come out like this, I become a narrow minded fool.
You are a narrow minded fool.
- Teacher.
- Hello.
Are the two of you perverts, huh?
Yesterday you were loving each other to death
today starting in the morning you're at each others' throats.
I know that there's no other man like Jung Hoon out there.
So I don't know why I'm so harsh with my words to him.
That wasn't right how I treated him when he skipped breakfast to bring me to work.
Do you think I need to rethink this marriage?
Don't rethink the wedding,
and fix your personality.
How long do you think Jung Hoon is going to let it go and just keep taking it?
Your mother wasn't right to you either.
How much is this?
What's that?
It's yummy.
Why are you here again?
You cleaned up everything.
You think I came because I wanted to?
I can't live knowing that I owe someone a debt.
Wow Dong Bi, you're different than others.
Now even if I wanted to come back again, I'm out of excuses.
-Should we be friends? -What do you mean about that?
It means we need to update our relationship status.
We can't go back to how we were before.
When the word 'used' is said between a man and a woman, that means it's the end of it.
Our relationship as lovers is over.
and I won't do that tacky thing of trying to glue the broken pieces of that together.
And what if I said I don't want to be friends?
-Then that's the end.
- I've already seen this through the end.
If you don't want to, forget it. I won't force you.
I'll do it.
Being friends - let's try it.
Want some wine?
I'm sorry for being a mad.
Thank you don't say you're sorry
I'm home!
Why are you back so early?
Why aren't you out with Jung Hoon?
I'm seeing him tomorrow.
I'm going to pay my respect to his parents.
- Want to go on a blind date? - Mom!
It's someone Ho Yong's mom knows
And I heard that he is going to inherit a whole shopping mall.
He's really intelligent, so they want a woman who's intelligent and witty.
I heard they want a teacher for a daughter-in-law,
Forget it, forget it. You already gave your permission, so what are you doing now?
I'm going over to Jung Hoon's tomorrow, remember? You already forgot?
I'm suggesting it because it's a waste.
What do you mean, being wasted?
Stop what you're doing, and just quit it altogether.
I'm going to marry Jung Hoon.
Oh right, mom!
- Why?
The money that I gave you, how much did you saved?
What money?
What do you mean, what money?
You've taken care of all my paychecks, and I've been getting allowances from it.
Why are you asking for that money now?
To get married I need money.
Why would you need any money?
You just need to take care of the basics.
And it''s not like you're going to be playing once you're married. You will be working.
It's fine if you don't have money.
Anyways, even if it's for the basics, give me my money now.
I don't have any.
My business isn't even doing well enough to cover the rent for my space.
I used that money to pay rent, and for living expenses.
You used my money for it?!
That means it's gone!
How can I get married without money?
What about Aunt?
Why are you using my money first?
Your Aunt is going to die old and alone without even getting married.
so she should at least have some money.
How could I have touched her money?
That's why I'm telling you to marry someone who has lots of money!
There are plenty of men who'd love to marry a girl like you even if you had nothing.
Where are those people?
Let me see them!
Seriously. What is that matter with you?
Now I have nothing to offer!
What do you mean, nothing to offer?
A man should take care of that himself.
I have to take care of my own things why should I burden the man without everything?
That's not a burden, but love!
Your idea of love is leeching off of someone?
Why you little Sass!
There you go hitting again.
Since you don't have nothing to say to that!
Why keep a business that can't even cover its own rent?
Just get rid of it!
Ah it's difficult.
Hello?
Is this the car center?
What?
It's not the car center?
It's not.
Sorry, I thought I was calling the car center.
Wait a moment.
- Hey Prissy.
- There you go provoking me again.
- How are my clothes?
- Pretty.
You think they'll like the gift?
Mother, is there something I can help you with?
- Mother is there anything I can do?
- Just go sit down, you're still a guest here.
Mother, thank you.
For treating me to delicious meals out and also for inviting me over to cook for me too.
I'm scoring some brownie points so that you'll be good to us in the future.
Give me some brownie points too so that Father will look kindly upon me too.
He already liked you even before he met you,
Since you're the one Jung Hoon chose.
Didn't you see the way he was looking at you during dinner earlier?
I didn't see, Mother.
how was he looking at me?
I'm not going to tell you. Find out for yourself.
Mother, you're so loving.
- Me?
- Yes, I'd like to be like you.
The mood is good
Let's put out the gift you brought too.
I had no idea what to bring, so I worried about if for a long while.
You did well.
Anything too extravert would have felt like you were trying to bride us.
So I would not have like it.
This is nice and light.
It's tasty.
Thanks Mother.
Honey.. she's here as a guest today,
so shouldn't you be doing this?
See? How he looks after you over me already?
But his warm gaze is being directed towards you, not me.
Really? But I'm getting the glare from over there for ordering you around.
That's not it, Mom.
Getting another family member is really joyous thing.
I'm really glad that the two of you have decided to marry.
It's your time now.
Once the two of you are married,
your Mom and I are planning on moving down to the countryside to live.
Dad!
Build a small house down in the country, and run a hospital down there...
Your Mom and I are going to live on our own down there.
Your Father wants to spend some time with me now.
Since he wasn't able to do that when we were young.
Even though there are things that have worked out for us and things that have not...
I have been blessed in many ways by this world.
So I'd like to return some of the blessings I've been given back to the world.
Do as you would like, Dad.
We also started out very humbly, and it's gotten us where we are today.
Starting off like that and watching things grow is rather fun.
Mother and Father are so wonderful.
Let's not be any more or less,
and live as well as they do.
Nam Do Hyun Plastic Surgery?
-What are you trying to say?
- Are you Nam Do Hyun's wife?
That's right.
Nice to meet you.
I'm the car center.
What would you like to order? Oppa likes the coffee here.
He says he likes the Barista here.
It's a new product.
Doesn't it curl really well?
It does curl pretty well,
but it doesn't seem to lenghten.
Don't you have anything that lengthens?
We do have it.
- Here.
- How annoying... I have to apply it again.
I'll come back next time.
Please give me the cleansing set.
- Stop by next time, okay?
-Ajumma, can't you give me another set?
I'll come back next time.
Make sure you come back again.
What a jerk.
Why did you give her everything she asked for?
She's still a customer.
I'm just grateful to anyone that stops in during bad economy like this.
How did it go over at Jung Hoon's?
There wasn't anything special since I already met his Mother a while ago.
But his dad is impressive.
How so?
After we're married, he's going to donate all his wealth to people in need.
And move down to the countryside.
- What?! Then you guys?
- What about us ?
What are they going to leave you?
How would I know?
What do you think is the reason for me allowing this wedding to happen?
If you're not guaranteed the money, then this can't happen.
Contact Jung Hoon!
How can I ask him that before we're even married?
Marriage boils down to money.
You know very well yourself how hard I worked to raise you girls after your Dad died.
- Still, that's a little...
-Then you just keep it still.
-Then you stay still, Mom will go.
- No, I'll do it.
Jung Hoon and I are the ones getting married here!
It should be a decision made by the two of us.
You think just anyone can make the choice and the decision?
Is the man you chose financially independent?
Ultimately, it's his parents that are going to foot the bill for the wedding.
But the money they're supposed to give you is gone now,
so what wedding?
We'll start off in a rental!
Mother said that they started out very humbly too and got to where they are now.
We can do that too! Is Jung Hoon a doctor?
He will be making less money than you his whole life!
Even so, he's still earning money!
That's all that matters!
Who are you calling in the middle of our conversation ?
I'm calling Jung Hoon!
After hearing what you said, there's no way I can allow this marriage to happen.
You stupid
You can't.
Hello?
Who is it?
They hung up.
Deul Ja (Mom): Hand it over. Jung Min: Don't do it. I will mind my own matters.
Okay.
What are you going to do about dinner?
Want me to bring you something?
Stop pretending to care about me like that and just take care of your own future.
What's wrong with my future?
You think I'm going to give up just because you're acting like that?
Jung Hoon,
It's Hae Yoon's mom,
my call got dropped earlier.
Do you have any free time today?
Do Hyun seems to prefer the dripped coffee over espresso.
Is my husband the same Do Hyun that you keep talking about ?
You must like checking things out.
I came out to see what kind of a girl you are, but I think I can rest easy now.
Break up with Do Hyun.
We've been seeing each other for three years.
If Do Hyun was just having fun,
he wouldn't have dated me for three years.
You've never asked for anyone to break up before, have you ?
You've never asked anyone to choose between you and a man's family before, right?
If you had, you wouldn't have met up with me.
There's been other women besides you.
But it's the first time I've met anyone who actually had hopes like you do.
I did some research. . .
but you used to be a nursing assistant too.
It's not like you're any better than me when it comes to your background.
and since you got to where you are by breaking up his previous family.
you have no lef to stant on either, right?
I've already calculated everything before I came out to meet you.
I don't... play games that I can't win.
I'm sure you've figured this in your calculation too, right?
Breaking up a family and worming your way in isn't as easy as you think it is.
I'm not going to be respectful to you anymore and just treat you however I see fit.
This is how these things play out.
I've put up with all that to be where I am.
I won't give up my spot easily.
I already know that it won't be easy.
But there's one thing that's different.
I have a son.
If you're going to win, you better come up with a new plan.
There's a huge difference between having a kid or no kid.
I know that you tricked him into marriage with a pregnancy.
A kid ? I can have one too.
I'm not on any birth control.
I'll teach you one trick as to how you can win..
Try to convince the man instead of stepping up yourself.
The face that you're here itself means that you've already lost.
You're overreacting because you've lost your confidence after meeting me.
Because my youth and beauty is so blinding.
It's something that you can never have yourself again.
Crazy girl.
Yes, how could I stell something that's not mine unless I'm crazy?
I'm not going to hit you or insult you.
Sorry.
You may not know since you're still young...
but you'll realize after some time passes, how foolish you were.
When that time comes,
You're going to hurt yourself and insult yourself.
Live with my husband.
Once you start living with him,
You'll realize there's nothing special to the man you stole.
And also that the only thing you can trust,
is ultimately, yourself.
Mother!
I called you out even though I know you're busy because I couldn't leave the store.
It's okay.
I'll come no matter what if you call me.
Your words are so flattering.
I heard our Hye Yoon went your house.
Yes.
Here, drink it.
It's delicious, having come from you.
I heard that your parents are really wonderful.
Hae yoon told me herself.
The reason why I wanted to see you is about meeting with your parents.
When would be good for them ?
They said they'll leave both next weekend and the weekend after that empty.
When would be good for you?
Hae Yoon told me...
That your father has decided to do something really great?
Ah.. giving back to the society?
Yes, giving back to the society.
How is that going to work?
How is it going to work?
For example.. is he just giving away the hospital or the house?
I don't really know myself.
Why do you ask ?
I was just wondering if my daughter has the qualification for such a family like that.
Mother, please don't say that!
Hae Yoon is over-qualified and then some!
Mom, here's your food.
Mom!
Why did you call Jung Hoon?
What do you mean?
She wanted to talk about the meeting with my parents.
- He's right.
- Let's go
Mother's not done speaking yet.
I'll relay the rest of her message, so just follow me out.
Goodbye.
How could you have addressed me like that?
That's no way to talk in front of Mother!
Mother won't think very highly of me now!
You should have told me that my Mom called you over!
Look at how you're changing the subject.
Then I have to speak up to you in front of her?
That's silly!
Even if you don't speak up to me,
you should have respected me.
Is me seeing your Mother something for you to be upset about?
The thing I'm upset about is that you didn't tell me about it first.
What difference would it make if I told you about it first?
I don't want you to see how low she can be.
It's really difficult catering to all your moods.
How are you catering to me.
If it's too difficult, then let's quit!
There you go with that again!
How can you say that so easily?
I don't say it easily.
We're about to get married...
We have to discuss everything before we do anything!
What are you saying we haven't discussed?
How can you say that?
There you go changing the subject again.
You don't love me, do you?
That's why you don't take me seriously, and keep dragging out the subject.
If you truly loved me, you have to accept what I'm saying.
Fine.. How can I beat you with words?
I was wrong. Even if I wasn't, I am.
Are you satisfied now?
You're not being sincere right now either.
What does it mean you were wrong even if you really weren't?
I'm being sincere. How can you believe that I'm being sincere?
- Get down on your knees.
- Right here ?
- We're in the middle of a street.
- You said you loved me.
Then why can't you do it ?
Forget it. I don't like my man getting down on his knees.
You don't want me to do it now?
Just the fact that you were willing to do it is enough.
It really is difficult matching your moods.
I'm hungry. Let's get some dinner.
No, I have to get home.
Go eat with your mother.
- There you go.
- Good luck selling.
Yes.
What did you say to Jung Hoon?
Don't leave anything out and tell me everything.
I didn't say anything to embarrass you, so don't worry.
Mom, please! Just leave it to us!
After seeing how he was today,
he was nice and compliant.
After looking only at Do Hyun's face, I liked how he tried to please me.
He's perfect for your personality.
I told you, that I chose him after careful consideration.
Let's meet his parents quickly.
I doubt they'll leave him penniless when he's their one and only child.
You seriously drive me crazy!
What did Hae Yoon's mother say?
Why did she want to see you?
It was about meeting you guys.
What about it?
Hae Yoon said she'd let me know.
If Hae Yoon was going to let you know, why did she ask to see you?
It's because she likes me.
I told you that she welcomed me with open arms when I went over to meet her.
She was very nice and sweet.
Give me some dinner.
She sent you away without even feeding you if she's that sweet on you ?
Mom, I'm going to get changed.
Want to see my muscles since it's been awhile?
Fine, fine..
I'll set the table, so come on down.
What is it that you're looking for?
I'm not buying.
I just wanted to look around.
- Are you going to ride it yourself?
- Yes
This one has a lower seat so it's safer, and it's easy to control.
So, this one is very popular with ladies.
If you're looking for speed and thrill, something like this would be more fitting.
- It's beautiful.
- What are you doing here?
Are you going to buy a bike?
Then, I'll be back.
Deul Rae... Deul Rae!
Deul Rae!
Lee Deul Rae.. Deul Rae!
What are you doing here?
What is it that you're doing here then ?
It's a given that I should come here.
this is the largest bike shop.
Goodbye.
I have to get back to work now.
Deul Rae, Lee Deul Rae...
Why do you keep calling my name ?
Do you want
me to take you there on my bike?
I can take you to the Children's House.
You like motorcycles, don't you ?
You keep seeing them in your head, don't you?
What are you saying right now?
That's how I got started too.
It's nice to be shopping with you like this.
This is all your stuff.
Why are you only buying things for yourself for the meeting with her Mom ?
- Don't you even feel guilty ?
- What would you like ?
Buy me a watch.
There's one I have my eye on.
No, not a watch. You'll get wedding gifts from her family anyways.
Tell Hae Yoo to buy it for you.
How can I ask her to buy something that costs 500,000 won?
I'm sure she's on that much sinces it's her wedding gift to you.
And you're upsetting me a little.
You don't feel bad about taking my money
but you don't want Hae Yoon spending hers?
-It's not like that.
-I'm mad.
You are a bad son.
Welcome.
-That's a little young for you.
It's a gift for Yae Hoon.
She doesn't know anything about designer brands.
She said people who buy designer things
is to make up for their lack of confidence.
I've caught you again.
Does that means that I buy designer things
because of my lack of confidence?
No, it's no that.
She prefers practical things.
That's because you don't know women.
It's because Hae Yoon's family isn't wealthy enough to do anything about it
But Yae Hoon is going to change once she becomes my daughter in law.
I thought you were out shopping with you Mother?
Then, why are you here?
I think we should spent some part of the weekend together.
I was about to get mad if you didn't come.
I figured that's why I came.
We didn't part in such good spirits last time after arguing.
And we pass the date of the meeting through the phone also.
-Did you hate me then?
- No, I hated myself.
I felt pathetic for acting like that.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to go crazy.
I'm falling in love with you again
Why is it that I can't hate you?
It's your fate. Accept it.
Don't fight it.